http://www.wallplate.com/pages/privacy-policy

Effective date: July 18, 2019
AmerTac is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy establishes our practices with regard to data collection, storage and usage when a user interacts with any of AmerTac’s Westek Brand of Smart devices. In this privacy policy, “personal data” means information that can be used to identify an individual, either from that information alone, or from that information and other information we have access to about that individual. Personal data is also commonly known as Personally Identifiable Information (herein referenced as PII), and can include personal data and personal data combined with non-personal data. We collect both personal and non-personal data to facilitate the best user experience possible.
INFORMATION COLLECTED AND HOW IT IS USED
In order to provide our services to you, we ask you to provide certain necessary personal data. If you do not provide your personal data, we are not able to provide you with our products or services.
Account Information
Personal data that is collected through the creation of an AmerTac or Westek Brand Account may include PII, which could include your email address or mobile phone number. Additionally, your nickname, profile picture, country and time zone will be connected to your account so that you can visit our product and service conveniently. All of this information helps us to activate, manage and provide AmerTac’s services to you.
User Mobile Phone Information
Your device model, operating system, unique device identifier, IP address, AmerTac or Westek Brand software version number, access type and model, etc. are required for you to receive PUSH notifications and access our services.
Smart Device Information
All the smart device information collected can be accessed and controlled via the app remotely and we automatically collect device information. This information includes the MAC address of your devices, IP address, wireless connection information, operating system type and version, application version number, push notification identifier, log files, and mobile network information.
Picture/Video
The picture or video acquired by your camera will be collected for certain products. They are used to afford mobile monitoring and alarm services to you if applicable.Depending on the different Smart Devices you elect to connect with our Products or Services, we may collect different information reported by your Smart Devices. For example, smart weights or fitness trackers may report your height, weight, body fat mass (BFM), BMI and skeletal muscle mass (SMM); smart cameras may report images or videos captured by it.
Feedback
We are always open to receiving your feedback and suggestions to ensure the quick resolution of problems or issues. When using feedback and suggestion features in our Products, we will collect your email address, mobile phone number and your feedback content to address your problems and solve device failures on a timely basis.
Infrared Information
Your infrared remote control information will be collected. This enables you to control other infrared equipment through the app if applicable to your product purchased.
User Scenario
When you use the scenario and automation functions, we will collect your setting information. This helps us provide intelligent scenario services to you.
HOW PERSONAL DATA IS USED
The information collected from you is used to control the smart devices you have purchased from us. Specifically, this data is used:
To provide you with our products and services, which includes processing your orders, performing contractual obligations between us, to ensure the functions and safety of our products, to verify your identity, to prevent and trace fraudulent or inappropriate usage.
To develop our products and services, together with general and statistical information.
To communicate with you, including providing you with notifications on products and services that are updated or launched.
To provide marketing and promotional materials to you on our products and services (please note that you may unsubscribe anytime).
To personalize product design and to provide you with services tailored to you. For example, we may recommend and display information and advertisements regarding products suited to you. You may be invited to participate in surveys relating to your device.
To conduct investigations regarding our products and services.
To provide maintenance services, monitor software licenses, to improve our products or analyze the efficiency of our operations.
Additionally, if you participate in any AmerTac lottery, contests or promotions that may be available periodically, we may use your personal data to manage such activities.
WHO CAN ACCESS YOUR INFORMATION
Unless explicitly stated in this privacy policy, your personal information will be kept confidential. Disclosure may include the scenarios listed in this section below. In each case described in this section, you can be assured that AmerTac will only share your personal data in accordance with your consent. AmerTac will ensures that any third party given access to your information is subject to our privacy practices and is required to comply with the relevant data protection and privacy laws of the United States.
AmerTac will contractually ensure compliance by any foreign Third Party Service Providers with the privacy standards that apply in your home jurisdiction.
DISCLOSURE TO A THIRD PARTY
AmerTacmay disclose your personal data without further consent if required or permitted by law in the following:
Cases in which the disclosure is required or authorized based on the applicable laws and/or regulations;
Cases in which the disclosure is necessary to respond to an emergency that threatens the life, health or safety of the individual or another individual;
Cases in which the disclosure is necessary for the prevention of crime or legal proceedings;
Cases in which the purpose of such disclosure is clearly in the individual’s interests, and if consent cannot be obtained in a timely way;
Cases in which the disclosure is necessary for any investigation or proceedings;
Cases in which the disclosure is to any officer of a prescribed law enforcement agency upon production of written authorization signed by the head or director of that law enforcement agency, or a person of a similar rank, certifying that the personal data is necessary for the purposes of the functions or duties of the officer; and/or
Cases in which the disclosure is to a public agency and such disclosure is necessary in the public interest.
To our customers and other business partners who provide you, directly or indirectly, with your Smart Devices, and/or networks and systems through which you access and use our Sites and Services.
NON-PERSONAL DATA/OTHER
We use statistical data that does not specifically identify you (non-personal data) to help in our operations and improve our products and services to provide a better user experience for you. Here are some of the non-personal data we may collect and how it is used:
When you create an AmerTac or Westek Brand Account, download our software, register on our website, participate in online surveys or interact with us in other ways, we may collect your language preferences, postal code, area code number and time zone in which you use our products and services, as well as your profession.
When you opt-in to participate in our User Experience Improvement Program, we may gather statistics relating to your use of our products’ functions on an anonymous basis. This may include information relating to your use of our official website, products and services. If there is an abnormal shutdown or breakdown, we may collect information relating to your mobile device to diagnose the problem.
When you use our services or functions that are based on location information, e.g. carry out a location search, take advantage of advertising, use weather functions, access information based on maps, etc., we may collect your geographical information.
When you use our website, online services, interactive applications, email messages and advertising, we may use cookies and other technical elements (e.g. pixel labels) to collect and store non-personal data. These enable us to provide you with a better experience and improve our overall service quality, e.g. in saving your preferred language settings, sending emails in a readable format, to determine whether the emails have been opened or not, etc.
When you use the Internet browser in using our products and services, we may collect log information, e.g. IP address, browser type, language, reference source, operating system, date and time marking and click rate data. When you first use and activate your Smart device, the device’s unique identification code and approximate geographical information may be collected.
TRANSFER INFORMATION
If you need to transfer the information in your account, please contact us via email at CustomerService@AmerTac.com.
RIGHT TO REFUSAL/OPT-OUT/TERMINATE SERVICES
You have confirmed that you have received, read, and understand all the content contained in this privacy policy before you use AmerTac services and you agree to all the provisions of this personal information policy. If you do not agree with this personal information policy, you will not be able to use the service provided by us.
If you prefer, you can delete all the following information via “Profile > Personal center > Terminate the Account” in the App:
Account Information
User Mobile Phone Information
Smart Device Information
Picture/Video
Feedback
Infrared Information
User Scenario
INFORMATION SAFEGUARDS
Various preventive measures will be taken to protect your personal information from loss, theft and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. In order to ensure the security of your personal information, our company has explicit information security regulations and procedures, and we have a dedicated information security team to strictly implement the above measures within the company.
INFORMATION RETENTION PERIOD
We will retain your information for the period necessary to achieve the purposes set out in this personal information protection policy, unless required or permitted by law to do so for a longer period.
COMPLAINTS AND FEEDBACK
If you have any questions or concerns about our personal information policy or data processing, contact us at CustomerService@AmerTac.com.
POLICY UPDATE
We may revise and update this policy at any time. In the event that changes will need to be made, we will issue a notice published on our website 30 days in advance. If you continue to use the related services of the AmerTac and Westek Brand Smart platform on the date when the amendment update officially takes effect, the continued use of our services will constitute an agreement to our revision update.
Links
Home
Our Products
Product Support
Where to Buy
About Us
Contact Us
AmerTac
Monday - Thursday: 8AM - 4:30PM EST Friday: 7AM - 3:30PM EST
Copyright © 2020 AmerTac Inc. — All Rights Reserved
